export const quizQuestions = [
    {
        question: "Which nation won the UEFA Euros 1992 despite not even qualifying?",
        options: ["Germany", "England", "Denmark", "Czech Republic"],
        correctAnswer: "Denmark",
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the highest goalscorer in England's Premier League?",
        options: ["Thierry Henry", "Wayne Rooney", "Alan Shearer", "Harry Kane"],
        correctAnswer: "Alan Shearer",
    },
    {
        question: "Which nation has won the most FIFA World Cups?",
        options: ["Argentina", "Brazil", "England", "Italy"],
        correctAnswer: "Brazil",
    },
    {
        question: "What is Gareth Bale's favorite sport, (besides football)?",
        options: ["Rugby", "Golf", "Ice hockey", "Cricket"],
        correctAnswer: "Golf",
    },
    {
        question: "Which goalkeeper ended up playing ice-hockey after his football career?",
        options: ["Petr Čech", "Iker Casillas", "Gianluigi Buffon", "Edwin van Der Sar"],
        correctAnswer: "Petr Čech",
    },
    {
        question: "Who holds the record for scoring the most goals in the FIFA World Cup history?",
        options: ["Ronaldo", "Miroslav Klose", "Pelé", "Lionel Messi"],
        correctAnswer: "Miroslav Klose",
    },
    {
        question: "Which football club holds the nickname, The Red Devils?",
        options: ["Arsenal", "Chelsea FC", "Liverpool FC", "Manchester United"],
        correctAnswer: "Manchester United",
    },
    {
        question: "Which football player once famously said, I don't believe in luck... I believe in hard work and bananas?",
        options: ["Cristiano Ronaldo", "Zlatan Ibrahimovic", "Romelu Lukaku", "Mario Balotelli"],
        correctAnswer: "Romelu Lukaku",
    },
    {
        question: "Which football player once set off fireworks in his own bathroom?",
        options: ["Paul Pogba", "Mario Balotelli", "Kylian Mbappe", "Zlatan Ibrahimović"],
        correctAnswer: "Mario Balotelli"
    },

    {
        question: "Who is the best sporting director in the world?",
        options: ["Super-Bo Andersson", "Ralf Rangnick", "Silvio Berlusconi", "Florentino Pérez", "Deco"],
        correctAnswer: "Super-Bo Andersson"
    }
];